David Mozersky African Union High-Level Implementation Panel Papers MS205
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Sudan Post-referendum negotiation files, 1998 -- 2012; MS205.004; 405 Digital Object(s)
  - Economic negotiations strategy, 2009 -- 2011; MS205.004.00012
    - ABD Planning meeting, 2011; MS205.004.00013
      - Notes Economic Planning Meeting with ADB, AUHIP Staff, 2011-01-23 -- 2011-01-25; MS205.004.00015
      - Summary of Economic Pplannin Meeting with ADB, AUHIP Staff, 2011-01-23; MS205.004.00016
    - Ben Leo papers, 2011; MS205.004.00017
      - Alternative Paris Club Treatments, 2011-01-10; MS205.004.00018
      - Sudan Debt Apportionment - Technical Note, 2011-01; MS205.004.00019
      - Debt Options Paper - Outline, 2011-01-30; MS205.004.00020
      - Assets and Liabilities Sub-Cluster - AUHIP Debt Proposal, 2011-02; MS205.004.00021
      - NCP Position on External Debt - Key Takeaways - Based on 12 January 2011 Meeting with NCPEconomic Team, 2011-01-14; MS205.004.00022
      - NCP Economic Team Brief - Debt Issues - Suggested Points/Questions, 2011-01-12; MS205.004.00023
      - NCP Economic Team Brief - Debt Issues - Suggested Points/Questions, 2011-02-02; MS205.004.00024
      - Sudan Debt Model, 2011-02-02; MS205.004.00025
      - Debt Devision - Options and Key Issues, 2011-01-08; MS205.004.00026
    - Economic seminar, 2010; MS205.004.00029
      - Concept Note Workshop on Priority Economic Issues, 2010-12-12 -- 2010-12-13; MS205.004.00030
      - Annotated Agenda: Workshop on Priority Economic Issues, 2010-11-27; MS205.004.00031
      - Revised Concept Note Workshop on Priority Economic Issues, 2010-12-12 -- 2010-12-13; MS205.004.00032
      - Agenda Workshop on Priority Economic Issues, 2010-11-27; MS205.004.00033
      - Concept Note - Seminar on Priority Economic Issues, 2010-12-12 -- 2010-12-13; MS205.004.00034
      - Workshop on Priority Economic Issues - Contextualization and Outputs, 2010-12-12 -- 2010-12-13; MS205.004.00035
      - Concept Note Workshop on Priority Economic Issues - Clean, 2010-12-12 -- 2010-12-13; MS205.004.00036
      - Annotated Agenda: Workshop on Priority Economic Issues, 2010-11-26; MS205.004.00037
      - Revised Concept Note Workshop on North-South Economic Cooperation, 2010-12-27; MS205.004.00038
    - Fred Quarshie papers, 2011; MS205.004.00039
      - Options for the Currency Sub-Cluster Negotiations, 2011-02-03; MS205.004.00040
      - Draft Inputs into Proposed Economic and Financial Discussions in Addis Ababa on the Weekend of 23-25th January 2011, 2011-01-23 -- 2011-01-25; MS205.004.00041
      - Requestion Macroeconomic Data from Sudan, 2011-02-02; MS205.004.00042
      - Some Notes and Questions to be Asked during Discussions between AUHIP and SPLM Scheduled for 4th Feb 2011, 2011-02-04; MS205.004.00043
    - NCP debt papers and strategy, 2009 -- 2011; MS205.004.00045
      - NCP Paper - Post Referendum Arrangements - External Debt Resolution Strategy, 2011-01-15; MS205.004.00046
      - NCP Paper - Post Referendum Arrangements - External Debt Resolution Strategy, 2011-01-15; MS205.004.00047
      - NCP Paper - Post Referendum Arrangements - External Debt Resolution Strategy, 2011-01-15; MS205.004.00048
      - NCP Paper - Post Referendum Arrangements - External Debt Resolution Strategy, 2011-01-15; MS205.004.00049
      - Sudan External Debt Position as of 31st December 2009, 2009-12-31; MS205.004.00050
  - A strategy for negotiations on economic issues, MS205.004.00027
  - Dialogue on North-Sourth Economic Cooperation, 2011-01-24; MS205.004.00028
  - NCP Economic Team Briefing for AUHIP on Debt, Currency and Economic Negotiations, 2011-01-12; MS205.004.00044
  - NCP Economic Team Brief: Talking Point and Questions, 2011-01-11; MS205.004.00051
  - Economic Strategy Paper - Building up the Elements of an Economic Agreement, 2011-01-20; MS205.004.00052
  - Debt Division - Options and Key Issues, 2011-01-08; MS205.004.00053
  - Framework, 2010; MS205.004.00054
    - Agreement on a Framework for Resolving Outstanding Issues Relating to the Future of Sudan and the Comprehensive Peace Agreement, 2010-10-24; MS205.004.00055
    - Borders SRZ Concept Note, 2010-10-26; MS205.004.00056
    - Draft Framework Skeleton, 2010-10-24; MS205.004.00057
    - Draft General Principles - NCP and SPLM Strategic Agreement on their Post-CPA Relationship and Guidelines for Post-Referendum Issues, 2010-10-25; MS205.004.00058
    - Framework for Resolving Outstanding Issues Relating to the Implementation of the Comprehensive Peace Agreement and Future Relations of North and South Sudan, 2010-11-13; MS205.004.00059
    - Framework for Resolving Outstanding Issues Relating to the Implementation of the Comprehensive Peace Agreement and Future Relations of North and South Sudan, 2010-11-13; MS205.004.00060; African Union High-level Implementation Panel
    - Framework Agreement on CPA and Post-CPA Arrangements Concept Note, 2010-10-20; MS205.004.00061
      Confidential Draft Internal AUHIP only
  - Invitations, 2010 -- 2011; MS205.004.00062
    - Draft Letter from Thabo Mbeki to SPLM/NCP Post-Referendum Lead Negotiation Panel - PRI Invitation, 2010-11-26; MS205.004.00063
    - Draft AUHIP Letter to Minister of Defence H.E. Lt-Gen Abdel Rahim Mohamed Hussein - Invitation for Meeting in Khartoum February 2011, 2011-02-03; MS205.004.00064
    - Draft AUHIP Letter to Minister of SPLA Affairs H.E. Mr Nhial Deng Nhial - Invitation for Meeting in Khartoum February 2011, 2011-02-03; MS205.004.00065
    - Draft Letter - Invitation for Economic Negotiations, 2011-02-03; MS205.004.00066
    - Letter from AUHIP to H.E.Idriss Abdulgadir (NCP) on the Meeting on Economic Issues, 2011-02-03; MS205.004.00067
    - Letter from Thabo Mbeki to H.E. Lt-Gen Abdel Rahim Mohamed Hussein, Minister of Defence - Invitation for Security Meeting on February 8, 2011, 2011-02-03; MS205.004.00068
    - Letter from Thabo Mbeki to H.E. Vice President Dr Riek Machar Teny - Invitation for Border Meeting, 2011-02-06; MS205.004.00069
    - Letter from Thabo Mbeki to H.E. Vice President Ali Osman Taha - Invitation for Border Meeting, 2011-02-06; MS205.004.00070
    - Draft Letter - Economic Negotiations in Addis Ababa Delayed, 2011-02-08; MS205.004.00071
    - Draft Letter to H.E. Vice President Riek Machar - Postponement of the Governors Consultation/Borders Conference, 2011-02-17; MS205.004.00072
    - Letter from Abdul Mohammed (AUHIP) to Haile Menkerios (Special Representative of the Secretary General, UNMIS) - Invitation for Economic Talks March 1-5 2011, 2011-02-22; MS205.004.00073
    - Letter from Abdul Mohammed (AUHIP) to Amb Princeton Lyman - Invitation for Economic Talks March 1-5 2011, 2011-02-22; MS205.004.00074
    - Letter from Thabo Mbeki to H.E. President Omar al-Bashir - Invitation to Attend Meeting on Abyei, 2011-03-06; MS205.004.00075
    - Letter from Thabo Mbeki to H.E. First Vice President Salva Kiir Mayardit - Invitation to Attend Meeting on Abyei, 2011-03-06; MS205.004.00076
    - Letter from Thabo Mbeki to Hon Lt-Gen Abdel Rahim Mohamed Hussein, Minister of Defence - Invitation for Security Meeting, 2011-03-06; MS205.004.00077
    - Letter from Thabo Mbeki to Hon Nhial Denh Nhial, Minister for SPLA Affaris - Invitation for Security Meeting, 2011-03-06; MS205.004.00078
    - Letter from Thabo Mbeki to H.E. Idriss Abdulgadir and H.E. Pagan Amum Okiech - Super Group Invitation May 2011, 2011-04-20; MS205.004.00079
    - Draft Letter from Thabo Mbeki to Omar Ahmad Al-Bashir - Update on Spring Meeting with the World Bank and IMF, 2011-04-25; MS205.004.00080
    - Draft Letter from Thabo Mbeki to Salva Kiir Mayardit - Update on Spring Meeting with the World Bank and IMF, 2011-04-25; MS205.004.00081
    - Letter from Thabo Mbeki to Minister Idriss Abdelgader - Invitation for Super Group Meeting May 2011, 2011-05-10; MS205.004.00082
    - Letter from Thabo Mbeki to Minister Pagum Amum - Invitation for Super Group Meeting May 2011, 2011-05-10; MS205.004.00083
    - Draft Letter from Thabo Mbeki to Minister Idriss Abdelgader on Meeting - Invitation for Final Round of Negotiations June 8-11 2011, 2011-06-06; MS205.004.00084
    - Invitation to follow up meeting on Economic issues in Ethiopia, 2011-03-22; MS205.004.00480
  - Lead panel, 1998 -- 2012; MS205.004.00085
    - 2010-11-28 meeting, MS205.004.00086
      - Annotated Agenda: Meeting with NCP/SPLM Lead Panel, 2010-11-28; MS205.004.00087
      - Post Referendum Negotiation Cluster Groups: Progress Report 27/11/10, 2010-11-27; MS205.004.00088
    - 2010-12-08 meeting, MS205.004.00089
      - Annotated Agenda for 8-9 December - Meeting with Lead Negotiating Panel, 2010-12-06; MS205.004.00090
      - Talking Points for the Chair on the Annotated Agenda - 8-9 December Meeting with Lead Negotiating Panel, 2010-12-06; MS205.004.00091
      - Proposed Agenda for 8-9 December Meeting with Lead Negotiating Panel, 2010-12-08; MS205.004.00092
      - Thoughts on the 8-9 December Meeting, 2010-12-08; MS205.004.00093; Mozersky, David
    - Cluster reporting, 2010; MS205.004.00094
      - Citizenship Notes: Issues Requiring Political Guidance from the Lead Negotiating Panel, 2010-12-08; MS205.004.00095
      - Consolidated list of Issues Requiring Political Guidance from the Lead Negotiating Panel, 2010-12-09; MS205.004.00096
      - Economics and Natural Resources Notes, 2010-12-08; MS205.004.00097
      - Report of the Joint Financial, Economic and Natural Resources Working Group, 2010-12-08; MS205.004.00098
      - Key Economic Points - Economic Cluster, 2010-12-08; MS205.004.00099
      - Security Notes - Issues Requiring Political Guidance from the Lead Negotiating Panel, 2010-12-08; MS205.004.00100
      - Summary of Issues Requiring Political Guidance from the Lead Negotiating Panel, 2010-12-09; MS205.004.00101
      - Treaties - Issues Requiring Political Guidance from the Lead Negotiating Panel, 2010-12-08; MS205.004.00102
      - Treaties Notes - Issues Requiring Political Guidance from the Lead Negotiating Panel, 2010-12-08; MS205.004.00103
    - Minutes, 2010; MS205.004.00104
      - Final Meeting AUHIP/Lead Negotiating Panel - Minutes, 2010-12-08; MS205.004.00105
      - Progress Made in Post-Referendum Arrangements, 2010-12-14; MS205.004.00106
      - Lead Negotiating Panel Cluster Meeting - Minutes by Neha, 2010-12-08; MS205.004.00107
      - AUHIP Meeting - Minutes Simon, 2010-12-08; MS205.004.00108
    - 2010-12-13 meeting, MS205.004.00109
      - Agenda December 13 Meeting of the Lead Negotiating Panel and AUHIP, 2010-12-12; MS205.004.00110
      - Annotated Agenda for December 13 Meeting, 2010-12-13; MS205.004.00111
      - Summary of Citizenship Working Group, 2010-12-13; MS205.004.00112
      - Citizenship Cluster Break-Out Session, 2010-12-13; MS205.004.00113
      - Consolidated list of Issues Requiring Political Guidance from the Lead Negotiating Panel, 2010-12-09; MS205.004.00114
      - Party Positions on Priority Issues, 2010-12-12; MS205.004.00115
      - Tasks for Cluster Break Out Groups, 2010-12-13; MS205.004.00116
      - Reports from the meeting, 2010; MS205.004.00117
        - AUHIP Meeting With SPLM and NCP Cluster Group Co-Chairs - Minutes, 2010-12-13; MS205.004.00118
      - Cluster group minutes, 2010; MS205.004.00119
        - Citizenship Cluster Break-Out Session, 2010-12-13; MS205.004.00120
        - Post Referendum Arrangements Security Cluster - Minutes, 2010-12-13; MS205.004.00121
      - Cluster summary reports, 2010; MS205.004.00122
        - Citizenship Working Group Summary - Meeting of SPLM/NCP Lead Negotiating Panel and AUHIP, 2010-12-13; MS205.004.00123
        - Outline for Final Agreement Financial, Economic and Natural Resources - Presentation of the Joint Cluster, 2010-12-13; MS205.004.00124
        - International Treaties and Other Legal Issues Cluster Group, 2010-12-13; MS205.004.00125
        - Security Cluster - Agreed/Disagreed Points, 2010-12-13; MS205.004.00126
        - Security Cluster - Points of Disagreement, 2010-12-13; MS205.004.00127
    - 2010-12-18 meeting, 1998 -- 2010; MS205.004.00128
      - Proposals, 1998 -- 2010; MS205.004.00129
        - Drafts of borders proposal, 2010; MS205.004.00130
          - Draft Letter First Vice-President Ali Osman Taha, Vice-President Riek Machar Teny - Border Proposal, 2010-12-21; MS205.004.00131
          - Introductory Note on AUHIP Proposal on Border Issues, 2010-12-17; MS205.004.00132
          - Agreement Between the Government of the Republic of Sudan and the Sudan People's Liberation Movement on Cross Border Issues, 2010-12-19; MS205.004.00133
          - Draft Agreement on Cross Border Issues Between the Government of the Republic of Sudan and the Sudan People's Liberation Movement, 2010-12-27; MS205.004.00134
        - Final submitted proposals, 1998 -- 2010; MS205.004.00135
          - Letter from Thabo Mbeki to H.E. Vice-President Riek Machar Teny on Border Agreement, 2010-12-23; MS205.004.00136
          - Draft Agreement on Cross Border Issues Between the Government of the Republic of Sudan and the Sudan People's Liberation Movement, 2010-12-28; MS205.004.00137
          - Draft on Citizenship Agreement - Specific Commitments on Nationality, Citizenship and Related Issues, 2010-12-17; MS205.004.00138
          - Final Draft Agreement Between the Government of Sudan and the Sudan People's Liberation Movement on Currency and Banking Issues, 2010-12-17; MS205.004.00139
          - Ecowas Transhumance Agreement, 1998; MS205.004.00140
          - Frame Agreement between the Government of the Republic of Sudan and the Government of Southern Sudan Concerning the Petroleum Sector, 2010-12-17; MS205.004.00141
        - Talking points, 2010; MS205.004.00142
          - Additional Issues Tasked to the Lead Negotiation Panel at the Dec. 13 Meeting (Beyond Oil, Currency and Citizenship), and Positions of the Parties, 2010-12-13; MS205.004.00143
          - Post Referendum Citizenship - Proposed Process to Finalize Agreement, 2010-12-17; MS205.004.00144
          - Post Referendum Currency - Proposed Process to Finalize Agreement, 2010-12-17; MS205.004.00145
          - Introductory Remarks to Meeting on Oil, Currency and Citizenship, 2010-12-18; MS205.004.00146
          - Issues Tasked to the Cluster Groups at the Dec. 13 Meeting, 2010-12-13; MS205.004.00147
          - Post Referendum Oil Issues - Proposed Pocess to Finalize a Heads of Agreement, 2010-12-17; MS205.004.00148
      - Sunday economic meeting, 2010; MS205.004.00149
        - Economic Issues Notes, 2010-12-18; MS205.004.00150
        - Economic Workshop Notes, 2010-12-18; MS205.004.00151; James, Laura
        - Oil and Currency Redemption Joint Report, 2010-12-18; MS205.004.00152; James, Laura
        - Economic Inter-Linkages between Northern and Southern Sudan - Talking Points, 2010-12-18; MS205.004.00153
        - Economic Inter-Linkages between Northern and Southern Sudan - Talking Points, 2010-12-19; MS205.004.00154
    - 2011-02-04 SPLM Economic meeting, 2010 -- 2011; MS205.004.00155
      - SPLM Economic Team and AUHIP Meeting Notes, 2011-02-03; MS205.004.00156
      - SPLM Economic Team Brief: Talking Points and Questions, 2011-02-02; MS205.004.00157
      - Government of Sudan/National Congress Party Response to Disclosure Request of the Sudan People's Liberation Movement/Government of Southern Sudan, 2011-02-03; MS205.004.00158
      - Economic, Finance and Natural Resources Working Group - Sudan People's Liberation Movement/Government of South SudanKey Positions and Required Action Points on the Negotiation Process, 2011-02-03; MS205.004.00159
      - Progress Report from the Sudan People's Liberation Movement/Government of South Sudan Working Group on Economic, Financial and Natural Resources Issues, 2010-12-07; MS205.004.00160
      - Consolidated List of Issues in Economic, Finance and Natural Resources Working Group Requiring Political Guidance from the Lead Negotiating Panel, 2010-12-09; MS205.004.00161
      - Sub Group on Currency and Banking Balance Sheet - Disclosure by Central Bank of Sudan, 2010-12-31; MS205.004.00162
      - Key Indicators for Southern Sudan, 2010-12-14; MS205.004.00163; Southern Sudan Centre for Census, Statistics and Evaluation
        Statistical information on South Sudan (data on population; education; water, health and sanitation; poverty and consumption; household characteristics; businesses and economic activity).
        South Sudan; Statistical data; Southern Sudan Centre for Census, Statistics and Evaluation
      - Outline for Final Agreement - Joint Cluster Financial, Economic and Natural Resources, 2010-12-13; MS205.004.00164
    - 2011-03-01 Economic negotiations, 2010 -- 2011; MS205.004.00165
      - Report on the NCP/GoS - SPLM/GoSS Economic Negotiations, 2011-03-01 -- 2011-03-05; MS205.004.00166
      - Options for the currency sub-cluster negotiations, MS205.004.00167
      - Assets and Liabilities Sub Cluster - AUHIP Debt Proposal, 2011-02-08; MS205.004.00168
      - Agendas, 2011; MS205.004.00169
        - Annotated Agenda North-South Economic Dialogue, 2011-03-01; MS205.004.00170
        - Annotated Agenda North-South Economic Dialogue - Final, 2011-03-01; MS205.004.00171
        - Draft Talking Points - Closing Remarks: Final Session and the Way Forward, 2011-03-01; MS205.004.00172
        - Annotated Agenda North-South Economic Dialogue, 2011-03-01; MS205.004.00173
        - Draft Agenda - Internal Planning Meeting for Economic Negotiations, 2011-02-28; MS205.004.00174
        - Negotiation agendas, 2011; MS205.004.00175
          - Addis Negotiation - Debt Agenda, 2011-02-28 -- 2011-03-05; MS205.004.00176
          - Finance, Economic and Natural Resource Cluster Oil Sub Group - Continuation of Roadmap Meetings - Agenda, 2011-03-02 -- 2011-03-05; MS205.004.00177
          - Finance, Economic and Natural Resource Cluster Oil Sub Group - Continuation of Roadmap Meetings - Agenda, 2011-03-02 -- 2011-03-05; MS205.004.00178
          - Currency Sub Cluster Negotiations in Debre Zeit Ethiopia - Draft Proposed Agenda, 2011-03-02 -- 2011-03-05; MS205.004.00179
      - Issue papers for seminar, 2011; MS205.004.00180
        - Economic Dialogue - Issues Paper on Macroeconomic Cooperation - Sudan: Macroeconomic Prospects and a Framework for Macroeconomic Cooperation for Two Viable Economies in the Short to Medium Term, 2011-03-01; MS205.004.00181; Geda, Alemayehu
        - The Macroeconomic Cooperation Framework for North and South Sudanese Negotiation on Oil, Debt and Currency during the Transition Period, 2011-03-01; MS205.004.00182; Geda, Alemayehu
        - The Macroeconomic Cooperation Framework for North and South Sudanese Negotiation on Oil, Debt and Currency during the Transition Period - Presentation, 2011-03-01; MS205.004.00183; Geda, Alemayehu
        - Economic Dialogue - Issues Paper on Oil, 2011-03-01; MS205.004.00184
        - Economic Dialogue - External Debt Issues Paper, 2011-03-01; MS205.004.00185
        - Economic Dialogue - Issues Paper on Currency, 2011-03-01; MS205.004.00186
      - Minutes and agreements, 2011; MS205.004.00187
        - Currency, 2011; MS205.004.00188
          - Currency Session 1 - Minutes, 2011-03-01; MS205.004.00189
          - Currency Session 1 Sub Group Meeting - Points of Agreement, 2011-03-02; MS205.004.00190
          - Currency Session 1 - Minutes, 2011-03-02; MS205.004.00191
          - Currency Session 2 Sub Group Meeting - Points of Agreement, 2011-03-03; MS205.004.00192
          - Currency Session 2 Sub Group Meeting - Minutes, 2011-03-03; MS205.004.00193
          - Currency Session 3 Sub Group Meeting - Points of Agreement, 2011-03-04; MS205.004.00194
          - Currency Session 3 - Minutes, 2011-03-04; MS205.004.00195
          - Agreed Final Minutes of the Sub Group on Currency and Banking, 2011-03-05; MS205.004.00196
        - Debt, 2011; MS205.004.00197
          - Debre Zeit Round - Final Facilitation Record of 1-4 March Discussions, 2011-03-01 -- 2011-03-04; MS205.004.00198
          - Debre Zeit Round - Facilitation Record of 2 March Discussions As Presented, Amended and Endorsed by the Parties on 3 March, 2011-03-02 -- 2011-03-03; MS205.004.00199
          - Debre Zeit Round - Facilitation of Record of 3 March Discussions As Presented, Amended and Endorsed by the Parties on 4 March 2012, 2011-03-03 -- 2011-03-04; MS205.004.00200
          - Draft Debt Relief Letter - Joint NCP-SPLM, 2011-03-04; MS205.004.00201
          - Sub Cluster on Assets and Liabilities - Summary Points, 2011-03-04; MS205.004.00202
          - Debre Zeit Round - Sub Cluster on Assets and Liabilities - Final Version Summary of Decisions, 2011-03-04; MS205.004.00203
        - Oil, 2011; MS205.004.00204
          - Finance, Economic and Natural Resource Cluster Oil Sub Group - Continuation of Roadmap Meetings Addis Ababa - Agenda, 2011-03-02 -- 2011-03-05; MS205.004.00205
          - Economic Dialogue - Sudan Petroleum Sector: Post Secession Options - Presentation, 2011-03-01; MS205.004.00206; Hannevik, Anders
          - Economic Dialogue - Financial Transition Arrangement - Presentation, 2011-03-03; MS205.004.00207
          - Financial, Economic and Natural Resource Cluster Oil Sub Group - Introduction and Infrastructure - Presentation, 2011-03-02 -- 2011-03-05; MS205.004.00208
          - Issues Discussed between the Government of the Republic of Sudan/National Congress Party and the Government of Southern Sudan/the Sudan's Peopel's Liberation Movement - Concerning the Petroleum Sector, 2011-03-05; MS205.004.00209
          - Financial, Economic and Natural Resource Cluster Oil Sub Group - Updated Roadmap, 2011-03-02 -- 2011-03-05; MS205.004.00210
        - Paatti Talking Points, 2011-03-14; MS205.004.00211
        - Letter from Thabo Mbeki to Hon Pagan Amum Okiech and Hon Idris Abdelgadir - Consolidated Reports from the Meeting of the Economic, Finance and Natural Resources Cluster, 2011-03-06; MS205.004.00212
      - Options papers, 2010 -- 2011; MS205.004.00213
        - Drammen Petroleum Sector in Sudan - Options for Management of the Sector Following Secession in July 2011, 2011-02-08; MS205.004.00214
        - AUHIP Options Paper for Management of the Petroleum Sector in Sudan Following Secession in July 2011, 2011-02-16; MS205.004.00215
        - Draft Agreement between the Government of the Republic of Sudan and the Government of Southern Sudan Concerning the Petroleum Sector, 2010-12; MS205.004.00216
        - AUHIP Questionnaire for the Parties: To be read with the Economic Options Papers, 2011-02-16; MS205.004.00217
        - Assets and Liabilities Sub Cluster - AUHIP Debt Proposal, 2011-02-16; MS205.004.00218
        - AUHIP Options paper for the Currency Sub Cluster Negotiations, 2011-02-16; MS205.004.00219
      - Parties attendance lists, 2011; MS205.004.00220
        - NCP Attendees List - Post Referendum Arrangements (Oil, Currency, Debts) Addis Ababa Negotiations Round (1-5 March 2011), 2011-03-01 -- 2011-03-05; MS205.004.00221
        - SPLM Attendees List - Post Referendum Arrangements (Oil, Currency, Debts) Addis Ababa Negotiations Round (1-5 March 2011), 2011-03-01 -- 2011-03-05; MS205.004.00222
      - Position papers for seminar, 2011; MS205.004.00223
        - The Macroeconomic Cooperation Framework for North and South Sudanese Negotiation on Oil, Debt and Currency during the Transition Period, 2011-01-31; MS205.004.00224; Geda, Alemayehu
        - The Macroeconomic Cooperation Framework for North and South Sudanese Negotiation on Oil, Debt and Currency during the Transition Period - A Non-Technical Summary, 2011-02; MS205.004.00225; Geda, Alemayehu
    - 2011-04-05 Economic neogtiations, 2010 -- 2011; MS205.004.00226
      - Matrix of Preparations for April Economic Negotiation Round, 2011-03-10; MS205.004.00227
      - Next Steps, 2011-03-09; MS205.004.00228